strikingoffers.com 2010-01-13

# StrikingOffers

PRIVACY POLICY

StrikingOffers.com takes the privacy of its customers very seriously. Please read this Privacy Statement which sets out our Privacy Policy. The Privacy Policy sets out the terms which govern the collection, retention and processing of your personal information which we receive when you use this site. We recommend that you regularly check this page to review changes to this policy. Your continued use of this website constitutes your agreement to this policy and any changes to it.   
By using and / or disclosing your personal information to us using this website, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Statement.   
We operate in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and the Data Protection Principles ("the UK Data Protection Legislation").   
In instances where we collect email addresses we allow users to opt out at any time from receiving e-mail messages from us or from having information shared with third parties, including selected sponsors or business partners.  
We do not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes without providing you with a choice to opt out from such disclosure, which you can exercise during registration for any competition or service by mailing us at any time. 

**What Personally Identifiable Information of yours is collected**   
Information collected online is often defined as being either anonymous or personally identifiable. The amount of Personally Identifiable Information that you choose to disclose to us is completely up to you. We may at times ask you to submit information such as your name or email address, or to share your interests and hobbies with us. The type of information may include:   
\- Credit card information   
\- Information you provide when registering to receive goods or services from one or more of our partners.   
\- Information you provide when entering into a competition.   
\- Information you provide when filling out a user survey.   
\- Information you provide if you contact customer service.   
You never have to answer any questions, and you can decline this exchange of information at any time. However, if you should choose to withhold requested information, we may not be able to provide you with some of the services.  
When you surf the Internet, your Internet browser (such as Netscape Navigator(r) or Microsoft Internet Explorer) automatically transmits some information to StrikingOffers.com every time you access content on one of our sites. Examples of such information include the URL of the Web page you were just on (known as the "Refer"), the IP (or Internet Protocol) address of the computer you are using, or the browser version you are using to access our site. An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer when using the Internet. When you visit this website, our servers will log your IP address which we will use for administrative reasons. We may disclose your IP address to our service providers. All of this information may be collected by StrikingOffers.com and used to help improve our offerings to you.

**Correcting Inaccuracies in the information.**   
If the facility to register as a member of this website is offered you may access your account information and public profile by means of your user ID at any time. You will also be able to erase or deactivate your account by sending us an e-mail at requesting us to do this. Were we collecting personal demographic information about you we will offer the ability to access and edit the personal information that you have provided to us. To update the information retained about you, or to deactivate your account, please contact us.   

**The Use of Cookies**   
We use third-party advertising cookies to serve some of the ads that appear when you visit our Web site. A cookie is a small piece of information stored by a website on your computer's hard drive. Cookies are extensively used by websites as a convenient way to store information it knows about you. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites to provide advertisements about goods or services that may be of interest to you.   
An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer when using the Internet. When you visit the website our servers will log your IP address which we will use for administrative reasons. We may disclose your IP address to our service providers.   

**How StrikingOffers.com uses any information collected.**   
We use the personal information you supply us, including your registration data, to enhance our services, fulfil your requests for products, programs, or services, personalize your experience and provide you or permit others to provide you with special offers we think you will find valuable. We analyse the behaviour of our users, identifying their demographic characteristics and personal interests.   
We also use your registration data information in connection with the competitions and other promotions in order to track your progress, to notify you if you are a winner and to ensure that we comply with the applicable laws.   
We may also use the information we collect to develop summary reports for our advertisers. We provide this information to assist our advertisers in determining how to promote their products. We do not tell our advertisers who it was that saw or clicked on their advertisements unless you have told us this is acceptable.   
Unless you have opted out of receiving special offers, emails or other communications from selected third parties, we also may provide a report to our advertiser which tells them who responded to a particular offer. For example, we might send you an email, launch a new window within your internet browser, or send you other advertisements in electronic form which offer you a discount on a particular good or service. If you click on that e-mail or advertisement or accept an offer or discount contained therein, we may provide the advertiser with the information necessary to provide you with that discount or offer.   
StrikingOffers.com may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide Personally Identifiable Information to appropriate governmental authorities. If requested by law enforcement or judicial authorities, we will provide this information upon receipt of the appropriate documentation.   
Other companies that place advertising on our site may collect information about you when you view or click on their advertising or content through the use of cookies (using the same techniques as described above). Due to the way the Internet technically operates, we cannot control this collection of information. As the consumer you should contact these advertisers or content providers that place information on the website directly if you have any questions about their use of the information they potentially collect.   

**Do not disclose your email or password to unknown parties**   
The information that you voluntarily give over the Internet can be used by others. We cannot control the actions of visitors or non-registered Internet surfers. If you reveal private information, you do so at your own risk and must assume that this information can be collected and be used by others. You are responsible for keeping your e-mail address and password secret. You do not have to answer any email that requires you to give your password.

**The passing of information to third parties**   
Other than where you authorise us to disclose your personal data to third parties, your personal data will be treated as confidential. When you do authorise us to disclose your personal data to third parties we will only disclose it to the extent agreed. Where you have permitted us to pass your data to third parties, we will not be responsible for the use of your personal data by such third parties because the behaviour of such third parties will be outside of our control. Where your personal data is to be transferred out of the European Union, we will ask you for your specific consent to such transfer beforehand. In all cases where personal data is not going to be used solely by this website, you will be informed at the time the data is collected from you.
